# **PERRY WONG**

## Markham, ON, Canada

perry.w1224@gmail.com www.perry-wong.ca

647.299.4056 linkedin.com/perrywong1224

## **WEB DEVELOPER**

Create Code to Bring Concepts to Life, Enhance User Experience, and Cultivate Positive Branding

Curious web developer with a strong user-centric approach to provide quality services and products. Utilize logic and compassion and translate client needs into functioning, real-life technological solutions. Build software using the most appropriate coding language for each project and test performance on different browsers and devices. Prioritize and accomplish goals within tight deadlines.

Communicate complex ideas clearly, partnering with UX/UI and product designers, data analysts, and clients. Ask questions, offer solutions, and develop enjoyable customer products while efficiently capturing user data.

### **DEVELOPER SKILLS**

- Frontend: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript
- jQuery, Bootstrap
- REST API, Node, Express
- Cloud: AWS Lambda, Heroku, Google Firestore
- MERN and MEAN stack
- Angular, React, and React Native
- Mongo, PostgreSQL
- GitHub, Postman

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- 10 years in customer service and working in a team
- Speak fluent English, Japanese, and Cantonese
- Always holding accountability for my work

- Proactively approach others to offer help
- Actively listen and offer various solutions
- Prioritize tasks and use consistent time management

# **PROJECTS**

## CAREERFOUNDRY, BERLIN, GER 2022 –2022

#### **POKEDEX**

- Built with vanilla JavaScript, JSON, Bootstrap, HTML, and CSS you can search through 150 Pokémon utilizing the Pokémon API. See project here.
- The Pokedex project put a real test to my artistic ability with different colors as well as Bootstrap features such as the navigation bar. Being a developer, visual presentation is just as important as making the website run.

## **MY-FLIX APP**

- Built with MERN stack and Redux, this allows users to create their own profile, login, view the top 10 movies I entered in the database, add movies to favorites and remove them. See project here.
- This is the first project that taught me how to build both backend and frontend from scratch. This helped me build a solid base to create more future webpages using React.

### **MEET APP**

- Meet-App: This is a serverless progressive web app built in React. It uses AWS Lambda, OAuth2 through Google, and
  uses Google API to show events from various cities. Users can filter number of events and cities. See project here.
- The Meet-App project went through numerous unit testing to ensure the app can run error-free. This case study helped me understand the importance of running tests before publicizing.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

STOUFFVILLE FAMILY EYE CARE, Stouffville, ON MANAGER OPTICIAN, 2021 - PRESENT

- Assist clients with buying glasses, performing adjustments, and troubleshooting vision issues.
- Delegate tasks to other colleagues during peak times, proactive listening to patient's dissatisfaction about services and eyewear, inspect the product to ensure measurements and prescription are accurate.
- Strive for 100% customer satisfaction with tailored solutions, attentive service, and overall happy clients.

WARBY PARKER, TORONTO, ON OPTICIAN, 2019 –2021

### **EDUCATION**

WEB DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATION
CAREER FOUNDRY, BERLIN, GER 2022

**BACHELOR OF ARTS (BA), SPEECH COMMUNICATION**UNIVERISTY OF WATERLOO, WATERLOO, ON 2009